forexcapitalcs.com 2014-09-28

# Forex Capital CS

  1. ### ForexCapitalCS LTD Respects Each Individual's Right to Privacy

We realize how important it is for us to safeguard any personal information that may reveal your identity or account information, whether you are our client or a visitor to our Web site's public domain. To demonstrate our commitment to your security, we extend the following pledge to you. 
  2. ###  Your Privacy is Our Priority 

ForexCapitalCS Ltd. is committed to safeguarding the personal information you provide us. This privacy policy describes how we handle and protect personal information we collect about individuals who apply for or receive our products and services. The provisions of this notice apply to former clients as well as our current clients. 
  3. ###  How We Collect Personal Information

When you apply for or maintain an account with ForexCapitalCS Ltd, we collect personal information about you for business purposes, such as evaluating your financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, informing you about products and services that may be of interest to you, and providing client service. The personal information we collect about you includes: 
    1. information you provide to us on applications and other forms, such as your name, address, date of birth, Social Security number, occupation, assets and income.
    2. information about your transactions with us and with our affiliates.
    3. information we receive from consumer-reporting agencies, such as your credit history and creditworthiness, and other entities not affiliated with ForexCapitalCS Ltd. 
    4. information you provide to us to verify your identity, such as a passport, or received from other entities not affiliated with ForexCapitalCS Ltd.
  4. ###  How We Protect Personal Information 

We limit access to your personal information to those employees who need to know in order to conduct our business, service your account, and help you accomplish your financial objectives, such as providing you with a broad range of products and services. Our employees are required to maintain and protect the confidentiality of your personal information and must follow established procedures to do so. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. We do not rent or sell your name or personal information to anyone. 
  5. ### About Cookies

Cookies are small files containing information that a Web site uses to track its visitors. ForexCapitalCS Ltd may set and access ForexCapitalCS Ltd cookies on your computer, enabling us to learn which advertisements and promotions bring users to our Web site. ForexCapitalCS Ltd or any of its affiliates or divisions may use such cookies. 
  6. ###  About Hyperlinks

ForexCapitalCS Ltd Web sites may contain hyperlinks or "links" to other sites, and other sites may "link" to our sites. These Web sites that may be linking to or from ForexCapitalCS Ltd sites provide a separate privacy policy than ForexCapitalCS Ltd does. ForexCapitalCS Ltd privacy policy applies exclusively to ForexCapitalCS Ltd LTD and information collected by our Web sites. ForexCapitalCS Ltd is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of the sites you link to, nor do we have control over the use or security of information provided by you or collected by those sites. If you choose to link to one of these Web sites, you may be asked to supply registration or other information. It is important that you realize this information is going to a third-party, and you should become familiar with the privacy policy provided by that third-party. 
  7. ###  ForexCapitalCS Security Technology

ForexCapitalCS Ltd uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology in order to protect the information that you submit. This type of technology is designed to protect you from having your information intercepted by anyone other than ForexCapitalCS Ltd while it is being transmitted to us. We also use other safeguards such as firewalls, authentication systems (e.g., passwords and personal identification numbers) and access control mechanisms to control unauthorized access to systems and data. However, you acknowledge and accept that any services provided through the Website involve transmissions over the internet and that such transmissions are therefore subject to the internet’s inherent risks. Whilst we acknowledge our responsibility to take reasonable security precautions, you also acknowledge and accept that, as with any network, you may also be exposed to unauthorized programs transmitted by third parties, electronic trespassing and/or the failure of information and data to reach their intended destinations and/or erroneous receipt or misdirection of such information. Although our and our suppliers’ privacy and security features are designed to reduce these risks, we cannot guarantee their elimination. You therefore acknowledge that no transmission via the Website shall be guaranteed to be confidential and that we shall not be liable for any breach of confidence arising as a result of such event. 
  8. ###  Sharing Information with Our Affiliates

We may share personal information described above with our affiliates for business purposes, such as servicing client accounts and informing clients about new products and services, as permitted by applicable law. Our affiliates are companies controlled or owned by us, or companies controlling or under common control with us, and include financial service companies, such as dealers, other brokers, futures commission merchants and advisors. 
  9. ### Disclosure to Non-Affiliated Third Parties

In order to support the financial products and services we provide to you, we may share the personal information described above with third-party service providers and joint marketers not affiliated with us, including: 
    1. financial service institutions (advisors, dealers, brokers, trust companies and banks) with whom we have joint marketing agreements, such as agreements to market financial services or products that we jointly offer, endorse or sponsor.
    2. companies under contract to perform services for us or on our behalf, such as vendors that prepare and mail statements and transaction confirmations or provide data processing, computer software maintenance and development, transaction processing and marketing services. 
  10. These companies acting on our behalf are required to keep your personal information confidential. 
We may collect, use and disclose personal data about you, including personal data you may voluntarily disclose to us in any manner, so that we can (i) carry out our obligations with respect to any Services; (ii) carry out our everyday business activities and dealings with you; (iii) compile statistical analysis of the pages of the Website visited; (iv) monitor and analyze our business; (v) participate in crime prevention, legal and regulatory compliance, including screening and comparing such data against sanctions and other databases used for crime prevention purposes; (vi) market and develop other products and services; (vii) transfer any of our rights or obligations under the Services; and (viii) process your personal data for other related purposes. If you choose to withhold non-sensitive personal data requested, we will not be able to give you access to this Website. 
  11. ### Accessing and Revisiting Your Personal Information

You have certain rights of access to some or all of the personal data we collect and hold about you at the time of request, or to have inaccurate information corrected, under applicable data protection laws. If you wish to exercise such rights, you should contact us in writing, and may be requested to provide further information to assist us in complying with such request. Trading foreign exchange on margin carries a high level of risk, and may not be suitable for all investors. The high degree of leverage can work against you as well as for you. Before deciding to invest in foreign exchange you should carefully consider your investment objectives, level of experience, and risk appetite. The possibility exists that you could sustain a loss of some or all of your investment and therefore you should not invest money that you cannot afford to lose. You may be liable for losses that exceed the amount of margin that you post. You should be aware of all the risks associated with foreign exchange trading, and seek advice from an independent financial advisor if you have any doubts. 

     ©2013-2014 Forex Capital CS. All rights reserved
